---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://api.preview.platform.athenahealth.com/v1/19598472/chart/encounter/42917/questionnairescreeners
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      User-Agent:
      - Typhoeus - https://github.com/typhoeus/typhoeus
      Authorization:
      - Bearer oMrnCrlMvNfEmk5U9nJwsDDeHUjv
      Expect:
      - ''
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Thu, 26 Jan 2023 20:44:58 GMT
      Content-Type:
      - application/json; charset=UTF-8
      Content-Length:
      - '4987'
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      Server:
      - Apache
      Pragma:
      - No-cache
      Expires:
      - Mon, 06 Jan 1975 16:00:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-cache, no-store
      Accept-CH:
      - Sec-CH-UA-Platform-Version
      Vary:
      - Accept-Encoding
      Cneonction:
      - close
      X-RateLimit-Limit:
      - '50000'
      X-RateLimit-Remaining:
      - '49998'
      X-Request-Id:
      - rrt-871385933377322878-c-gea1-5741-169064498-2
    body:
      encoding: ASCII-8BIT
      string: '{"questionnairescreeners":[{"metaquestions":[{"questiontext":"Finding"}],"templatetype":"CUSTOM","templateid":1,"questionnaireid":2610,"scoringstatus":"UNSCORED","sections":[{"headertext":"Over
        the last two weeks, how often have you been bothered by any of the following
        problems?","questionlist":[{"key":"LITTLEINTEREST","questionid":1,"possibleanswers":["Not
        at all","Several days","More than half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Little
        interest or pleasure in doing things"},{"key":"FEELINGDOWN","questionid":2,"possibleanswers":["Not
        at all","Several days","More than half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Feeling
        down, depressed, or hopeless"},{"key":"TROUBLESLEEPING","questionid":3,"possibleanswers":["Not
        at all","Several days","More than half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Trouble
        falling or staying asleep, or sleeping too much"},{"key":"FEELINGTIRED","questionid":4,"possibleanswers":["Not
        at all","Several days","More than half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Feeling
        tired or having little energy"},{"key":"POORAPPETITE","questionid":5,"possibleanswers":["Not
        at all","Several days","More than half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Poor
        appetite or overeating"},{"key":"TROUBLECONCENTRATING","questionid":7,"possibleanswers":["Not
        at all","Several days","More than half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Trouble
        concentrating on things, such as reading the newspaper or watching television"},{"key":"BETTEROFFDEAD","questionid":9,"possibleanswers":["Not
        at all","Several days","More than half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Thoughts
        that you would be better off dead or of hurting yourself in some way"},{"key":"MOVINGORSPEAKINGSLOW","questionid":8,"possibleanswers":["Not
        at all","Several days","More than half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Moving
        or speaking so slowly that other people could have noticed? Or the opposite
        - being so fidgety or restless that you have been moving around a lot more
        than usual"},{"key":"FEELINGBAD","questionid":6,"possibleanswers":["Not at
        all","Several days","More than half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Feeling
        bad about yourself - or that you are a failure or have let yourself or your
        family down"}]},{"questionlist":[{"key":"HOWDIFFICULT","questionid":10,"possibleanswers":["Not
        difficult at all","Somewhat difficult","Very difficult","Extremely difficult"],"question":"If
        you checked off any problems, how difficult have these problems made it for
        you to do your work, take care of things at home, or get along with other
        people?"}]}],"documentids":[],"name":"PHQ-2\/PHQ-9"},{"templatetype":"CUSTOM","templateid":2,"scoreddate":"2023-01-23T10:08:38-05:00","questionnaireid":2590,"scoringstatus":"BEENSCORED","scoredby":"API-13361","sections":[{"headertext":"Over
        the last two weeks, how often have you been bothered by the following problems?","questionlist":[{"key":"TROUBLERELAXING","questionid":14,"answer":"More
        than half the days","possibleanswers":["Not at all","Several days","More than
        half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Trouble relaxing"},{"key":"FEELINGAFRAID","questionid":17,"answer":"More
        than half the days","possibleanswers":["Not at all","Several days","More than
        half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Feeling afraid as if something
        awful might happen"},{"key":"FEELINGNERVOUS","questionid":11,"answer":"More
        than half the days","possibleanswers":["Not at all","Several days","More than
        half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Feeling nervous, anxious or
        on edge"},{"key":"UNCONTROLLEDWORRYING","questionid":12,"answer":"More than
        half the days","possibleanswers":["Not at all","Several days","More than half
        the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Not being able to stop or control
        worrying"},{"key":"EASILYANNOYED","questionid":16,"answer":"More than half
        the days","possibleanswers":["Not at all","Several days","More than half the
        days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Becoming easily annoyed or irritable"},{"key":"TOOMUCHWORRYING","questionid":13,"answer":"More
        than half the days","possibleanswers":["Not at all","Several days","More than
        half the days","Nearly every day"],"question":"Worrying too much about different
        things"},{"key":"SORESTLESS","questionid":15,"answer":"More than half the
        days","possibleanswers":["Not at all","Several days","More than half the days","Nearly
        every day"],"question":"Being so restless that it is hard to sit still"}]}],"documentids":["205920"],"name":"GAD-7","score":327},{"templatetype":"SCOREONLY","templateid":66,"scoreddate":"2023-01-23T10:08:35-05:00","questionnaireid":2591,"scoringstatus":"BEENSCORED","scoredby":"API-13361","sections":[],"documentids":["205917"],"name":"Opioid
        Risk","score":77},{"templatetype":"SCOREONLY","templateid":95,"scoreddate":"2022-12-13T14:59:18-05:00","questionnaireid":2592,"scoringstatus":"BEENSCORED","scoredby":"API-13361","sections":[],"documentids":["205920"],"name":"CHADS2","score":327}],"totalcount":4}'
    http_version: '1.1'
    adapter_metadata:
      effective_url: https://api.preview.platform.athenahealth.com/v1/19598472/chart/encounter/42917/questionnairescreeners
  recorded_at: Thu, 26 Jan 2023 20:44:58 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.0.0
